PHILLIP SALOMAO

ABOUT ME

Hello, I'm Phillip and I have 23 years old. I'm a quite enthusiastic, self-motivated, responsible and hard working person. I'm a mature team worker and adaptable to all challenging situations. I am a dedicated, organized and methodical individual. I love studying data structure, high performance algorithms and economy books.

EDUCATION

Feb. 2018 – Feb. 2023 University of UNIFESO

• Bachelor in Computer Science

2006 – 2010 KUMON Mathematic course

Received mathematic certification

2007 – 2008 Index IT course

- Microsoft Office
- HTML3
- Operational System Windows
- Linux
- Database Editor

2020 - 2021

Front-end developer course

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- NodeJS
- MongoDB
- Next

EXPERIENCE

March 2020 – March 2021 SQA (Security Quality Assurance) internship at Alterdata Sofware

- Responsability to automate software with Delphi and C#
- Responsabilty for supporting clients.

November 2021 – Present Front-end developer at NOCLAF TECH

- Integrate REST API applications
- Develop UI with ReactJS / NextJS
- Work with Javascript / Typescript
- Styling with Ant Design and StitchesJS library
- Jest (React Testing Library)

Phone: +55 (21) 99538-0781

E-mail: philipsalomao99@hotmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/felipe-lippi-61b159199/

Github: https://www.github.com/SolomonDeveloper